[{"question": " i'd say from the looks of it; our naked buddy is moving.", "answer": " ironically, most of the boxes seem to be labeled clothes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " ohh, i'm gonna miss that big old squishy butt.", "answer": " and we're done with the chicken fried rice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " hey! hey! if he's moving, maybe i should try to get his place!", "answer": " good idea! yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " it would be so cool to live across from you guys!", "answer": " hey, yeah! then we could do that telephone thing! y'know, you have a can, we have a can and it's connected by a string!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh my god! i love this apartment! isn't it perfect?! i can't believe i never realized how great it is!", "answer": " well that is because your eye immediately goes to the big naked man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " it's amazing! you better hurry up and fill out an application or i'm gonna beat you to it.", "answer": "  ohh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  oh, look! there's monica and chandler!  hey! hey, you guys! hey!  ohh!! ohh! ahh-ahhh!!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  ahhh!! chandler and monica!! chandler and monica!!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " chandler and monica!!!!", "answer": " oh my god!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh!! my eyes!!! my eyes!!!!", "answer": " phoebe!! phoebe!! it's okay!! it's okay!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " no! they're doing it!!!", "answer": " i know!! i know!! i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " you know?!!!", "answer": " yes, i know! and joey knows! but ross doesn't know so you have to stop screaming!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  what's going on? phoebe and rachel: ohhh!!!", "answer": "  hi!! hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " what?! what?!", "answer": " nothing! oh god, we're just so excited that you want to get this apartment!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " you mean whenever monica and chandler where like y'know doing laundry or going grocery shopping or\u0097oh! all that time monica spent on the phone with sad linda from camp!", "answer": " uh-huh, doing it. doing it. phone doing it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh! oh, i can't believe it! i mean i think it's great! for him. she might be able to do better.", "answer": "  hey guys!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " joey! come here! come here!", "answer": " what? what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " phoebe just found out about monica and chandler.", "answer": " you mean how they're friends and nothing more?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " no. joey, she knows! we were at ugly naked guy's apartment and we saw them doing it through the window.  actually, we saw them doing it up against the window.", "answer": " okay, so now they know that you know and they don't know that rachel knows?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " yes, but y'know what? it doesn't matter who knows what. now, enough of us know that we can just tell them that we know! then all the lying and the secrets would finally be over!", "answer": " or, we could not tell them we know and have a little fun of our own.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " wh-what do you mean?", "answer": " well y'know every time that they say that like they're doing laundry we'll just give them a bunch of laundry to", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " ohhh, i-i would enjoy that!", "answer": " no-no-no! no-no wait rach, you know what would even be more fun? telling them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " ehhh, no, i wanna do phoebe's thing.", "answer": " i can't take any\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " no! you don't have to do anything! just don't tell them that we know!", "answer": " noo! i can't take any more secrets!  i've got your secrets. i've got their secrets. i got secrets of my own y'know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " you don't have any secrets!", "answer": " oh yeah? well, you don't know about hugsy, my bedtime penguin pal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": "  so umm, how-how are we gonna mess with them?", "answer": " ugh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " well, you could use your position y'know as the roommate.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " and then. i would use y'know the strongest tool at my disposal. my sexuality.", "answer": "  hello children!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " okay, watch, learn, and don't eat my cookie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey! ooh, wow that jacket looks great on you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " really?", "answer": "  yeah the material feels so soft\u0097hello mr. bicep! have you been working out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " well, i try to y'know, squeeze things.  are you okay?", "answer": " well, if you really wanna know, i'm\u0097oh! i can't tell you this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " phoebe, it's me. you can tell me anything.", "answer": " well actually you're the one person i can't tell this too. and the one person i want to the most.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " what's going on?", "answer": " i think it's just y'know that i haven't been with a guy in so long and how sometimes you're looking for something and you just don\u0092t even see that it's right there in front of you sipping coffee\u0097oh no, have i said to much? well it's just something to think about. i know i will.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " you are so cute! how did you get to be so cute?", "answer": " well, my grandfather was swedish and my grandmother was actually a tiny little bunny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " okay, now you're even cuter!!", "answer": " y'know that is a popular opinion today i must say.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " the weirdest thing happened at the coffee house, i think, i think phoebe was hitting on me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " what are you talking about?", "answer": " i'm telling you i think phoebe thinks i'm foxy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " that's not possible!", "answer": " ow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " i'm sorry it's just, phoebe just always thought you were, you were charming in a, in a sexless kind of way.", "answer": " oh, y'know i-i can't hear that enough.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " i'm sorry, i think that you just misunderstood her.", "answer": " no, i didn't misunderstand, okay? she was all over me! she touched my bicep for crying out loud!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " this bicep?", "answer": " well it's not flexed right now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " hey mon, what are you doing now? wanna come see a movie with us?", "answer": " uhh, y'know actually i was gonna do some laundry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " hey chandler, wanna do it with me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " sure, i'll do it with ya.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " okay great, hold on a sec!  oh, here you go! you don't mind do ya? that would really help me out a lot! thanks!", "answer": " i mean i-i don't i think i have enough quarters.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey ross! any word on the apartment yet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " well, i called over there and it turns out ugly naked guy is subletting it himself and he's already had like a hundred applicants.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " oh, is it that pinball machine with the big bow on it?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " that new mountain bike?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " well what did you send?", "answer": " a basket of mini-muffins.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " but there's a whole table of mini-muffin baskets. which one did you send?", "answer": " the small one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " what?! you-you actually thought that basket was gonna get you the apartment?", "answer": " well yeah! someone sent us a basket at work once and people went crazy over those little muffins. it was the best day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " your work makes me sad.", "answer": " oh man! i want that place so much!! i was so sure that was gonna work! there's twelve bucks i'll never see again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " all right honey, we'd better go if we wanna catch that movie.", "answer": " bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " bye!", "answer": " bye chandler!   i miss you already.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": "  okay, did you see that?! with the inappropriate and the pinching!!", "answer": " actually, i did!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " okay, so now do you believe that she's attracted to me?", "answer": " ohhh, oh my god! oh my god! she knows about us!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " are you serious?", "answer": " phoebe knows and she's just trying to freak us out! that's the only explanation for it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " phoebe knows about us!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " well i didn't tell them!", "answer": " them?! who's them?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " uhhh, phoebe and joey.", "answer": " joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " and rachel. i would've told you but they made me promise not to tell!", "answer": " oh man!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " i'm sorry! but hey, it's over now, right? because you can tell them that you know they know and i can go back to knowing absolutely nothing!", "answer": " unless\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " no! not unless! look this must end now!", "answer": " oh man, they think they are so slick messing with us! but see they don't know that we know that they know! so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " noooo.", "answer": " oh ross, honey you gotta stop torturing yourself!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " yeah, why don't you just find another apartment?", "answer": " look i've already looked at like a thousand apartments this month and none of them even compares to that one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " y'know what you should do?", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " you should find out what his hobbies are and then use that to bond with him. yeah! like if i would strike up a conversation about say umm, sandwiches. or uh, or my underwear.", "answer": " i'm listening.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  see?", "answer": " that is a great idea! and! i know ugly naked guy because we've been watching him for like five years so that gives me back my edge! oh, let's see now he had the trampoline.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " he broke that.", "answer": " well, he had gravity boots.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " yeah, he broke those too.", "answer": " so he likes to break stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " okay, i've got to go pick up ben but i-i will figure something out.  hey, didn't he used to have a cat?", "answer": " i wouldn't bring that up, it would probably just bum him out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " yeah, poor cat, never saw that big butt coming.", "answer": " right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " hello!  oh yeah! hey! hold on a second she's right here!  it's chandler.", "answer": "  oh?  hello you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " eh?", "answer": " well you know that thing you said before, i'd be lying if i said i wasn't intrigued.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah, listen, joey isn't gonna be here tonight so why don't you come over and i'll let you uh, feel my bicep. or maybe more.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " i'll have to get back to you on that. okay, bye!  oh my god! he wants me to come over and feel his bicep and more!", "answer": " are you kidding?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " i can not believe he would do that to mon\u0097whoa!  joey, do they know that we know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " they know you know.", "answer": " ugh, i knew it! oh i cannot believe those two!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " god, they thought they can mess with us! they're trying to mess with us?! they don't know that we know they know we know!  joey, you can't say anything!", "answer": " i couldn't even if i wanted too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " good evening, sir. my name is ross geller. i'm one of the people who applied for the apartment. and i-i realize that the competition is fierce but\u0097i'm sorry. i, i can't help but notice you're naked and  i applaud you. man, i wish i was naked. i mean, this-this looks so great. that is how god intended it.", "answer": " monica and rachel's, chandler and monica and rachel and phoebe are planning their respective strategies to break the other pairing. joey is not amused.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  look at them, they're-they're panicked!", "answer": " oh yeah, they're totally gonna back down!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " all right. all right! if he wants a date? he's gonna get a date. all right, i'm gonna go in.", "answer": " all right. be sexy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " so chandler, i-i'd love to come by tonight.", "answer": "  really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " oh absolutely. shall we say, around seven?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " show time!", "answer": " okay, rachel, get me perfume!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " all right, it'll be great! you just make her think you wanna have sex with her! it'll totally freak her out!", "answer": " okay, listen, how far am i gonna have to go with her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " relax, she-she's gonna give in way before you", "answer": " how do you know?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " because you're on my team! and my team always wins!", "answer": " at this?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": "  okay honey, now i'm gonna try to listen from right here!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " good idea!", "answer": " yeah, oh wait!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " phoebe.", "answer": " chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " come on in.", "answer": " i was going too.  umm, i brought some wine. would you like some?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " so, here we are. nervous?", "answer": " me? no. you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " no, i want this to happen.", "answer": " so do i.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " i'm gonna put on some music.", "answer": " maybe, maybe i'll dance for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " you look good.", "answer": " thanks! y'know, that when you say things like that it makes me wanna rip that sweater vest right off!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " well, why don't we move this into the bedroom?", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " oh, do you not want to?", "answer": " no. no! it's just y'know first, i wanna take off all my clothes and have you rub lotion on me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " listen, this is totally getting out of hand! okay? she wants me to put lotion on her!", "answer": " she's bluffing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " he's not backing down. he went to get lotion.", "answer": "  oh man! aren't you guys done yet?! i wanna sit in my chair!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " joey look, just look at it this way, the sooner phoebe breaks chandler the sooner this is all over and out in the open.", "answer": " ooh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " i like that!  oh, okay! show him your bra! he's afraid of bras! can't work 'em!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " joey!  wow, you didn\u0092t rip off any buttons.", "answer": " it's not my first time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " you go back out there and you seduce her till she cracks!", "answer": " okay, give me a second!  did you clean up in here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " of course. [cut back to the living room. chandler slowly exits the bathroom and gets pushed from behind by monica and sees phoebe closing the apartment door.)", "answer": " oh, you're-you're going?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " umm, not without you, lover.  so, this is my bra.", "answer": "  it's very, very nice. well, come here. i'm very were gonna be having all the sex.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " you should be. i'm very bendy.  i'm gonna kiss you now.", "answer": " not if i kiss you first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " ooh.", "answer": " well, i guess there's nothing left for us to do but-but kiss.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " okay! okay! okay! you win! you win!! i can't have sex with ya!", "answer": " and why not?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " because i'm in love with monica!!", "answer": " you're-you're what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " love her! that's right, i\u009alove\u009aher!!! i love her!!  i love you, monica.", "answer": " i love you too chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " i just\u0097i thought you guys were doing it, i didn't know you were in love!", "answer": " dude!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " and hats off to phoebe. quite a competitor.  and might i say your breasts are still showing.", "answer": " god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " all right! so that's it! it's over! everybody knows!", "answer": " well actually, ross doesn't.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " a new place for a new ross. i'm gonna have you and all the guys from work over once it's y'know, furnished.", "answer": " i must say it's nice to see you back on your feet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " well i am that. and that whole rage thing is definitely behind me.", "answer": " i wonder if its time for you to rejoin our team at the museum?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}]